TikTok decided to ban my account and this is my second account. And I just want to say to everyone
that this is a sign of the times. That account had over 180,000 followers, over millions in likes.
And that account wasn't just, you know, me talking about Palestine. Like that was also
an account of my life's work in the past two years, my independent filmmaking work where
I traveled to these places where I spoke to communities that, you know, have no voice in
the mainstream. And I tried to capture their voices and bring it to you guys, you guys in the
Western world. And, you know, unfortunately, a lot of people did not care, but I cared and their voices
mattered so much to me. And now we're watching a fucking genocide, man. And they're trying to
suffocate us into silence. Those voices of those communities mattered and they still matter. And
my message that if this is even my last video or like whatever, I just want to say something. And
I hope that everyone really can understand what I'm trying to say. It's that our struggles
as human beings is what unites us. That is something I learned from my independent project.
So far, I've learned that what's happening in Punjab, what's happening in Kashmir, it's not that
different from what's happening in Palestine, what's happening in Congo and Sudan and Tibet and Hong Kong
and the Uyghur Muslims. It's all the same shit. What's happening to the Kurds, what's happening in
Haiti, what's happening in Puerto Rico. These are just different levels, but it's the same shit,
different empires ruling over them. It is our struggles that unite us. So our liberation can
only happen in tandem. And my message to everyone is that if you are from a community that is being
stomped on and suffocated, unite, unite with all the other causes and move together. That is your
only chance of liberation. That is our, that is the only chance that we have as human beings to really
be free. You know, you can't say that, oh, we're going to take down Israel and things will be good. No,
we have to, we have to put an end to all the empires because if it's not America, it'll be another
empire and another empire waiting. If it's not America, it'll be China. If it's not China, it'll
be Russia. If it's not Russia, it'll be Iran. All of these empires are sick. We have to, we have to
change the system and we really can, but we have to unite our struggles. We have to show up for each
other and then we have to move together. So this is a call. This is a call to all peoples who are
fighting for the liberation of their people. Connect, make community, find it because right now they're
trying to, to silence us all.